Guide to the Francis Valentine Keesling Papers, 1906-1957
Department of Special Collections
- Series A. Political, 1906-1953
  - Subseries 3. Reference Material
    - International Organizations -- S.F. Conference, 1945 - 1947 (Box 22, Folder 192)
    - New Deal -- Truman Administration, 1945 - 1950 (Box 22, Folder 193)
    - Truman Administration, 1945, 1951 - 1952 (Box 22, Folder 194)
    - Recall Campaign -- Lapham, 1946 (Box 23, Folder 195)
    - National Municipal League, 1946 - 1950 (Box 23, Folder 196)
    - Intergovernmental Relations -- Santa Clara Co. Council on, 1946 (Box 23, Folder 197)
    - Municipal Campaign, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 198)
    - Municipal, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 199)
    - Municipal -- Advisory Committee to Mayor's Transportation Planning Council, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 200)
    - Traffic and Transportation -- Municipal, 1947 - 1951 (Box 23, Folder 201)
    - Municipal -- Traffic and Transportation, 1947 - 1951 (Box 23, Folder 202)
    - Intergovernmental Relations -- Santa Clara Co., 1947 (Box 24, Folder 203)
    - California State Campaign, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 204)
    - Constitutional Revision Committee, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 205)
    - National Policy, 1947 - 1951 (Box 24, Folder 206)
    - National Campaign, 1947 - 1948 (Box 24, Folder 207)
    - National Economy, 1 of 2, 1947 - 1951 (Box 24, Folder 208)
    - National Economy, 2 of 2, 1947 - 1951 (Box 24, Folder 209)
    - Labor, 1947 - 1948 (Box 25, Folder 210)
    - Education, general, 1 of 2, 1947 - 1953 (Box 25, Folder 211)
    - Education, general, 2 of 2, 1947 - 1953 (Box 25, Folder 212)
    - World Affairs, 1947 - 1948 (Box 25, Folder 213)
    - Federal Affairs, 1948 - 1952 (Box 25, Folder 214)
    - Republican Affairs, 1948 - 1952 (Box 25, Folder 215)
    - Constitutional Revision Committee, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 216)
    - California State Campaign, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 217)
    - Proposition # 3 -- anti-featherbedding, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 218)
    - Proposition # 4 -- aged and blind, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 219)
    - Initiative Proposals Ballot, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 220)
    - Proposition #14 -- state housing, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 221)
    - Special Legislation -- California Senate Reapportionment, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 222)
    - Municipal Campaign, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 223)
    - Election Contributions -- corrupt practices, etc., 1948 (Box 26, Folder 224)
    - Robinson Administration, 1 of 3, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 225)
    - Robinson Administration, 2 of 3, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 226)
    - Robinson Administration, 3 of 3, 1949 - 1950 (Box 26, Folder 227)
    - National Insurance Legislation, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 228)
    - Labor, 1948 - 1949 (Box 26, Folder 229)
    - Labor, 1948 - 1953 (Box 26, Folder 230)
    - Congress and California Legislature, 1948 - 1950 (Box 26, Folder 231)
    - National Republican, 1948 - 1950 (Box 27, Folder 232)
    - Liquor Control, 1948 - 1952 (Box 27, Folder 233)
    - Communism -- Russia, 1948 - 1952 (Box 27, Folder 234)
    - Municipal Campaign, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 235)
    - San Francisco Bond Screening Committee, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 236)
    - Municipal (S.F.) Bond Screening Comittee, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 237)
    - Proposals and Propositions Ballot, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 238)
    - California State Campaign, 1949 - 1950 (Box 27, Folder 239)
    - State Administration -- Warren, 1949 - 1950 (Box 27, Folder 240)
    - State Government and Legislature, 1949 - 1950 (Box 27, Folder 241)
    - Congressional Investigation, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 242)
    - Hoover Commission, 1949 (Box 28, Folder 243)
    - Hoover Commission, 1950 - 1952 (Box 28, Folder 244)
    - Labor -- Hawaiian Strike, 1949 (Box 28, Folder 245)
    - World Affairs, 1949 - 1953 (Box 28, Folder 246)
    - Municipal, 1950 - 1951 (Box 28, Folder 247)
    - Municipal Government Survey Commission, 1950 - 1951 (Box 28, Folder 248)
    - County (S.F.) Campaign, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 249)
    - California Legislation, 1950 - 1951 (Box 28, Folder 250)
    - Legislative Campaign -- Gambling Initiative, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 251)
    - Personal Property Initiative, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 252)
    - National Campaign, 1950 - 1952 (Box 29, Folder 253)
    - Election Returns, 1950 - 1951 (Box 29, Folder 254)
    - Patriotic Organizations, etc., 1 of 2, 1950 - 1951 (Box 29, Folder 255)
    - Patriotic Organizations, etc., 2 of 2, 1952 - 1953 (Box 29, Folder 256)
    - War -- Korea and U.N., 1950 - 1952 (Box 29, Folder 257)
    - Municipal, 1951 - 1953 (Box 29, Folder 258)
    - Municipal Campaign, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 259)
    - Municipal -- Flouridation, 1951 - 1952 (Box 29, Folder 260)
    - San Francisco Council of Churches, 1951 - 1953 (Box 29, Folder 261)
    - Y.M.C.A., 1951 (Box 29, Folder 262)
    - Legislation -- cross filing and primary, 1951 - 1952 (Box 30, Folder 263)
    - Legislation -- proposed liquor control, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 264)
    - Water Date -- California and elsewhere, 1951 - 1953 (Box 30, Folder 265)
    - Japanese Peace Treaty (Citizens Committee) and Japanese Peace Conference Citizens' Committee, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 266)
    - Municipal Campaign, 1952 - 1953 (Box 30, Folder 267)
    - Y.M.C.A., 1952 - 1953 (1936) (Box 30, Folder 268)
    - State Campaign, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 269)
    - Proposed Legislation, 1952 - 1953 (Box 30, Folder 270)
    - National Republican Campaign, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 271)
    - Eisenhower Administration, 1952 - 1953 (Box 30, Folder 272)
    - Sigma Nu Fraternity, 1 of 2, 1916 - 1953 (Box 30, Folder 273)
    - Sigma Nu Fraternity, 2 of 2, 1916 - 1953 (Box 31, Folder 274)
    - FVK Articles and Addresses, 1914 - 1928 (Box 31, Folder 275)
    - FVK Articles and Addresses, 1914 - 1928 (Box 31, Folder 276)
    - FVK Articles and Addresses, 1929 - 1951 (Box 31, Folder 277)
    - FVK Memos for Reference or Quotes, 1 of 2, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 278)
    - FVK Memos for Reference or Quotes, 2 of 2, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 279)
    - General Miscellany n.d. (Box 31, Folder 280)
    - Republican Convention and Progressive Party, 1 of 2 boxes, 1912 (Box 32)
    - Republican Convention and Progressive Party, 2 of 2 boxes, 1912 (Box 33)
    - FVK Gubernatorial Campaign, 1 of 2 boxes, 1914 (Box 34)
    - FVK Gubernatorial Campaign, 2 of 2 boxes, 1914 (Box 35)
    - CLIPS -- loose, 1914 - 1916 (Box 36)
    - Campaign Agent Johnson's Non-Partisan Scheme, 1 of 2, 1915, 1916 (Box 37)
    - Campaign Agent Johnson's Non-Partisan Scheme, 2 of 2, 1915, 1916 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Presidential Campaign and Hiram Johnson, 1924, 1932 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Primary Election Law, State Legislation, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Series B. San Francisco Charter, 1930-1953
  - Subseries 1. Correspondence Out
    - 1930; March - Dec. (Box 39, Folder 281)
    - 1931; Jan. - Dec. (Box 39, Folder 282)
    - 1932; Jan. - Nov. (Box 39, Folder 283)
    - 1933; Jan. - Nov. (Box 39, Folder 284)
    - 1934 - 1936 (Box 39, Folder 285)
    - 1937 - 1939 (Box 39, Folder 286)
    - 1940 - 1944 (Box 39, Folder 287)
  - Subseries 2. Correspondence In & General
    - A - B (Box 39, Folder 288)
    - C (Box 39, Folder 289)
    - D - H (Box 39, Folder 290)
    - I - M (Box 39, Folder 291)
    - N - R (Box 39, Folder 292)
    - S - Z (Box 39, Folder 293)
    - San Francisco A - F (Box 39, Folder 294)
    - San Francisco (Bureau of) Governmental Search, 1930 - 1940 (Box 39, Folder 295)
    - San Francisco H - Y (Box 40, Folder 296)
    - Miscellaneous Unidentified (Box 40, Folder 297)
  - Reference Material (printed material, clippings, etc.)
    - General -- Charter Revision (Box 40, Folder 298)
    - Drafts of Minutes, Board of Freeholders, 1930 - 1931 (Box 40, Folder 299)
    - Minutes -- Charter Installation Meetings, 1931 (Box 40, Folder 300)
    - Charter Story Copy and original draft, 1931 (Box 40, Folder 301)
    - Charter Story 1st galley Proof, 1931 (Box 40, Folder 302)
    - Charter Story copy and 2nd proof, 1931 (Box 40, Folder 303)
    - Assembly Concurrent Resolution # 26, 1 of 7, pp. 1 - 200 (Box 40, Folder 304)
    - Assembly Concurrent Resolution # 26, 2 of 7, pp. 201 - 227 (Box 41, Folder 305)
    - Assembly Concurrent Resolution # 26 -- Drafts, 3 of 7 (Box 41, Folder 306)
    - Assembly Concurrent Resolution # 26 -- Drafts, 4 of 7 (Box 41, Folder 307)
    - Assembly Concurrent Resolution # 26 -- Suggestions, 5 of 7 (Box 41, Folder 308)
    - Assembly Concurrent Resolution # 26 -- Suggestions, 6 of 7 (Box 41, Folder 309)
    - Assembly Concurrent Resolution # 26 -- Suggestions, 7 of 7 (Box 41, Folder 310)
    - Campaign Material (Box 41, Folder 311)
    - Speeches (Box 41, Folder 312)
    - Memo Reports and Calendar, 50, 61, 63, 68 (Box 42, Folder 313)
    - Memo Reports and Calendar, 1 - 49 (Box 42, Folder 314)
    - Memo Reports and Calendar, Supplemental, Calendar, and Ordinances (Box 42, Folder 315)
    - Memo Reports and Calendar (Box 42, Folder 316)
    - Data, 1 of 3, 1931 - 1936 (Box 42, Folder 317)
    - Data, 2 of 3, 1931 - 1936 (Box 42, Folder 318)
    - Data, 3 of 3, 1931 - 1936 (Box 42, Folder 319)
    - Data, 1937 - 1938 (Box 43, Folder 320)
    - Data, 1939 (Box 43, Folder 321)
    - Data, 1940 - 1943 (Box 43, Folder 322)
    - Municipal Affairs -- Traffic, Traffic School, 1 of 2 (Box 43, Folder 323)
    - Municipal Affairs -- Traffic, Traffic School, 2 of 2 (Box 43, Folder 324)
    - King vs. Leavy, 1932 (Box 43, Folder 325)
    - Charter copy in draft; Misc. Material, 1930 - 1934 (Box 43, Folder 326)
    - Miscellaneous Material re: Charter, 1930 - 1934 (Box 43, Folder 327)
  - Subseries 3. Reference Material
    - State Law Conflict, 1936 - 1938 (Box 44, Folder 328)
    - Holmes Investment Co. vs. S.F. Supervisors et. al., 1934, 1935 (Box 44, Folder 329)
    - Civil Service Commission, 1931 -1942 (Box 44, Folder 330)
    - Civil Service Constitutional Amendment, 1936 (Box 44, Folder 331)
    - S.F. Municipal Government, etc., 1912, 1913, 1916, 1941, 1942 (Box 44, Folder 332)
    - Pamphlets on S.F. Government, (7) (Box 44, Folder 333)
    - Miscellaneous, 1950 - 1953 (Box 44, Folder 334)
    - Charter -- leather-bound FVK personal copy, 1931 (Box 44, Folder 335)
    - Notebook (Box 44, Folder 336)
      - S.F. Charter, 1930 - 1933, June
      - Board of Freeholders Activities, etc.
      - S.F. Municipal Affairs Items, 1932 - 1934
      - Political
        - Coolidge Campaign, 1923 - 1924
        - Misc., 1924 - 1935
        - Hoover Campaign, 1928
        - Charter -- Bound final original draft
        - Clippings book, 1930, June - 1931, April
        - Clippings book, 1931, Apr. - 1934, Sept.
- Series C. Interim Committee of Twenty-Five (State Organization, 1936-1945)
  - Organizing Interim Committee, 1936 - 1938 (Box 47, Folder 337)
  - Organizing Interim Committee, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 338)
  - Organizing Interim Committee -- Minutes, 1936, Mar. 20 - 1937, June 12 (Box 47, Folder 339)
  - Organizing Interim Committee -- Notes (Box 47, Folder 340)
  - State Tax Conference -- Keesling's Diary, 1936 - 1938 (Box 47, Folder 341)
  - Sub-Committee on General State Organization and summaries of reports (Box 47, Folder 342)
  - Sub-Committee on General State Organization -- structure of administration organization and special funds, 1937 - 1938 (Box 47, Folder 343)
  - Sub-Committee on General State Organization -- structure of administration organization and tentative draft o f sub-com. report, 1938 (Box 47, Folder 344)
  - Sub-Committee General State Organization -- Administration (Box 48, Folder 345)
    - Organization - pamphlets (11)
    - U.S. Senate Report #1275
    - Draft #3 of act -- re: administration structure and function of executive department.
    - Report of President's Committee, 1937, Jan.
    - "Conflicting Taxation" 1935 progress report
    - (all loose material in front of box)
  - Sub-Committee on General State Organization -- Fiscal Reorganization -- pamphlets (11) (Box 48, Folder 346)
  - Sub-Committee on General State Organization 2 -- Fiscal Reorganization and misc. (Box 48, Folder 347)
  - Sub-Committee on General State Organization 3 -- Fiscal Reorganization and staff memos 3 & 5 1937 (Box 48, Folder 348)
  - Sub-Committee on General State Organization 3 -- Fiscal Report (Box 49, Folder 349)
  - Sub-Committee on Education, 1936 - 1939 (Box 49, Folder 350)
  - Sub-Committee on Education Report #2, 1936 (Box 49, Folder 351)
  - Sub-Committee on Education -- Reports 5 & 7, 1936 (Box 49, Folder 352)
  - Sub-Committee on Education -- staff letters, summaries of reports and Study of Local School Units in California, 1937 (Box 49, Folder 353)
  - Sub-Committee on Local Government (Box 49, Folder 354)
  - Sub-Committee on Highways and Public Works (Box 50, Folder 355)
  - Sub-Committee on Welfare, Relief, and Public Health, 1 of 2 (Box 50, Folder 356)
  - Sub-Committee on Welfare, Relief, and Public Health, 2 of 2 (Box 50, Folder 357)
  - Black Notebook -- com. (various) work sheets, outline, work done and not done (Box 50, Folder 358)
  - Tan Notebook -- similar to 358, more complete reports (Box 50, Folder 359)
  - Final Report -- galley sheets (Box 50, Folder 360)
  - Final Report -- typed copy in tan notebook (Box 51, Folder 361)
  - Final Report -- printed copies, letter of presentation to Governor and Legislature, clips (Box 51, Folder 362)
  - Omitted from Collection (Box 51, Folder 363 - 366)
  - Griffenhagen Reports (bound vol.) -- 1, 6, 9,10,45,80, and Staff Memos (Box 51, Folder 367)
  - Griffenhagen Reports (bound vol.) -- 11, 12, 13, 14, 16, 50 (Box 51, Folder 368)
  - Griffenhagen Reports (bound vol.) -- 17, 18, 19, 30, 31, 33, 36, 47, 82, 85, 88, 90 (Box 52, Folder 369)
  - Griffenhagen Reports (bound vol.) -- 20, 40, 41, 44, 62, 63, 64, 65, 66, 67, 68, 71, 78, 79, 86 (Box 52, Folder 370)
  - Griffenhagen Reports (bound vol.) -- 21, 29, 34, 38, 39, 43, 48, 60, 69, 70, 74, 83, 87, 89 (Box 53, Folder 371)
  - Griffenhagen Reports (bound vol.) - State Reorganization -- 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 37, 49, 61, 72, 73, 81, 84, 91 (Box 53, Folder 372)
  - Griffenhagen Reports (bound vol.) - State Colleges, Technical Schools -- 28, 32, 42, 51, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 77 (Box 54, Folder 373)
  - Griffenhagen Reports (bound vol.) - Public Education -- 58, 59, 75, 75 Appendix A and B, 76 (Box 54, Folder 374)
  - Committee Correspondence General File, 1 of 2, 1936 (Box 55, Folder 375)
  - General File, 2 of 2, 1936 (Box 55, Folder 376)
  - Minutes 1936, 1937 (Box 55, Folder 377)
  - Minutes 1938, 1939 (Box 55, Folder 378)
  - Governor's Conference and Appointment of Committee 1936, June - Mar. (Box 55, Folder 379)
  - Committee of Five, Employment of Griffenhagen and Associates, 1937 - 1939, 1941 (Box 55, Folder 380)
  - Committee of Five, Employment of Griffenhagen and Associates, 1941 (Box 55, Folder 381)
  - Griffenhagen and Associates -- Statements (financial), 1936 - 1937 (Box 55, Folder 382)
  - Griffenhagen and Associates Agreement, 1936 - 1937 (Box 56, Folder 383)
  - Griffenhagen and Associates Reports and General, 1936 - 1939 (Box 56, Folder 384)
  - Committee of Seven, 1936 (Box 56, Folder 385)
  - Rules Committee of Three, 1936 (Box 56, Folder 386)
  - Public Administration Service and other Public Service Institutions, 1936 - 1939 (Box 56, Folder 387)
  - Gross Income Tax Data, 1934 - 1936, 1944 (Box 56, Folder 388)
  - Finance, 1936 (Box 56, Folder 389)
  - Finance, 1937, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 390)
  - Pending and Unsettled Matters, 1937 - 1938 (Box 57, Folder 391)
  - General Solicitation (Box 57, Folder 392)
  - Cost of Government, 1934 - 1938 (Box 57, Folder 393)
  - Taxation, 1930 - 1940 (Box 57, Folder 394)
  - Executive Committee, 1937 - 1940 (Box 57, Folder 395)
  - Legislation and Correspondence, 1936, April - 1937 (Box 57, Folder 396)
  - Legislation and Correspondence, 1937 - 1941 (Box 57, Folder 397)
  - Legislation -- Bills and Amendments, 1936 - 1945 (Box 57, Folder 398)
  - Legislation and Initiative, Legislation Data, 1937, 1938, 1941 (Box 57, Folder 399)
  - Administrative including miscellaneious expenses, 1936 - 1941 (Box 57, Folder 400)
  - Release of Griffenhagen Reports, 1937, 1939, 1940 (Box 58, Folder 401)
  - Progress Report, 1936, 1937 - 1941 (Box 58, Folder 402)
  - Comments on Committee Work, 1937 (Box 58, Folder 403)
  - Organization -- internal and promotional, 1937, 1938, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 404)
  - Data on Organization, 1937 - 1944 (Box 58, Folder 405)
  - Sub-Committee, Project VIII (Revenue), 1937 (Box 58, Folder 406)
  - Sub-Committee on General State Organization (F.N. Belgrano, chairman), 1937 - 1938 (Box 58, Folder 407)
  - Nebraska Plan, University of California, 1937, 1938 1943 (Box 58, Folder 408)
  - Final Report -- Finalizing and Publication, 1936, 1941 (Box 58, Folder 409)
  - Distribution (Final Report), 1936, 1937, 1940 (Box 59, Folder 410)
  - Distribution (Final Report), 1941, Feb. - April (Box 59, Folder 411)
  - Distribution (Final Report), 1941, May - Oct. (Box 59, Folder 412)
  - Distribution (Final Report), 1941, Nov. - 1945 (Box 59, Folder 413)
  - Final Report -- Finalizing and Publication (Box 59, Folder 414)
  - Final Report -- Distribution Planning and Installation, 1942 - 1945 (Box 59, Folder 415)
  - Final Report -- Distribution Acknowledgements, 1941 - 1942 (Box 59, Folder 416)
  - Final Report -- Distribution Requests Refused, 1941 (Box 59, Folder 417)
  - Miscellaneous -- unidentified, etc. (Box 59, Folder 418)
  - Clipping Scrapbook (Box 60)
- Series D. Golden Gate Bridge, 1919-1957
  - General, 1923 - 1932 (Box 61, Folder 419)
  - General, 1933 - 1939, 1943, 1950 (Box 61, Folder 420)
  - Insurance, 1930 - 1935, 1937 (Box 61, Folder 421)
  - Finance, general, 1921 - 1957, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 422)
  - Bond Issue Campaign, 1930 - 1936 (Box 61, Folder 423)
  - Bond Syndicate, 1932 - 1939 (Box 61, Folder 424)
  - B-L Engineering Corp., Ltd. 1931, Apr. - June (Box 61, Folder 425)
  - Reconstruction Finance Corp., (Also PWA and Federal funds), 1927, 1930 - 1936 (Box 61, Folder 426)
  - Litigation, 1930 - 1933 (Box 61, Folder 427)
  - Speeches, 1933 - 1936, n.d. (Box 62, Folder 428)
  - Thomasini Bridge, 1935 (Box 62, Folder 429)
  - Building Com. -- general, 1927 - 1933 (Box 62, Folder 430)
  - Building Com. -- Color and Lighting Study, 1933 - 1935 (Box 62, Folder 431)
  - Building Com. -- Personnel, 1930, 1932 - 1934 (Box 62, Folder 432)
  - Building Com. -- Employment and Wage Scale, 1930 - 1936 (Box 62, Folder 433)
  - Building Com. -- Paint Tests 1930 - 1936 (Box 62, Folder 434)
  - Building Com. -- Cement, 1930 - 1936 (Box 62, Folder 435)
  - Building Com. -- Traffic, 1930 - 1936 (Box 62, Folder 436)
  - Building Com. -- Elevators, 1934 - 1936 (Box 62, Folder 437)
  - Building Com. -- Rapid Transit, 1930 - 1936 (Box 62, Folder 438)
  - Building Com. -- Tolls, 1936 (Box 62, Folder 439)
  - Building Com. -- Minutes and Reports, 1931 - 1936 (Box 62, Folder 440)
  - Building Com. -- McClintoc- Marshall Contract, 1931 - 1936 (Box 62, Folder 441)
  - Road Approaches, 1929 - 1934 (Box 63, Folder 442)
  - Road Approaches, 1935 (Box 63, Folder 443)
  - Road Approaches, 1936 - 1938, 47, n.d. (Box 63, Folder 444)
  - Military Replacements, 1934 - 1936 (Box 63, Folder 445)
  - Building Committee -- South Pier Kinzie Matter, 1931, 1933 - 1936 (Box 63, Folder 446)
  - Bailey Willis Matter, 1934, Apr. - Nov. (Box 63, Folder 447)
  - Bailey Willis Matter, 1934 - 1941 (Box 63, Folder 448)
  - Building Committee -- Board of Consultants, 1930 - 1934, 1936 (Box 63, Folder 449)
  - Joseph B.Strauss -- General, 1930 - 1939 (Box 64, Folder 450)
  - Applications for Employment -- Accounting and Clerical, 1931 - 1936 (Box 64, Folder 451)
  - Applications for Employment -- Stenographers, 1931 - 1933, 1937 (Box 64, Folder 452)
  - Applications for Employment -- Construction Men and Laborers, 1932 - 1934 (Box 64, Folder 453)
  - Applications for Employment -- Engineers and Inspectors, 1919, 1921, 1929 - 1934 (Box 64, Folder 454)
  - Applications for Employment -- Miscellaneous, 1930 - 1937 (Box 64, Folder 455)
  - J.B. Strauss -- Chief Engineer's Contracts 1929 - 1933 (Box 64, Folder 456)
  - J.B. Strauss -- Chief Engineer's Contracts 1934 (Box 64, Folder 457)
  - J.B. Strauss -- Chief Engineer's Contracts 1935 - 1937 (Box 64, Folder 458)
  - J.B. Strauss -- Chief Engineer's Reports, 1928, 1930 - 1934 (Box 65, Folder 459)
  - J.B. Strauss -- Chief Engineer's Reports, 1935 - 1937 (Box 65, Folder 460)
  - General Manager: Appointment and Reports, 1931 - 1935 (Box 65, Folder 461)
  - General Manager: Appointment and Reports, 1936 - 1942 (Box 65, Folder 462)
  - Inspections, 1931 - 1937 (Box 65, Folder 463)
  - Celebration Committee, 1932 - 1937 (Box 65, Folder 464)
  - San Francisco Exposition, (See also Public Relation), 1934 - 1935 (Box 65, Folder 465)
  - Dedication Address F.V.K., 1937, May - June (Box 66, Folder 466)
  - Dedication Address F.V.K., 1937, May - July (Box 66, Folder 467)
  - Board of Directors, 1923 - 1925, 1933 (Box 66, Folder 468)
  - Board of Directors, 1934 - 1935 (Box 66, Folder 469)
  - Board of Directors, 1936 - 1939 (Box 66, Folder 470)
  - Bids and Bidders, Contracts, and Contractors, 1929 - 1931 (Box 66, Folder 471)
  - Bids and Bidders, Contracts, and Contractors, 1932 - 1933 (Box 66, Folder 472)
  - Bids and Bidders, Contracts, and Contractors, 1934 - 1935 (Box 67, Folder 473)
  - Bids and Bidders, Contracts, and Contractors, 1936 - 1937, n.d. (Box 67, Folder 474)
  - Toll Plaza, 1931 - 1936 (Box 67, Folder 475)
  - Public Relations, (see also San Francisco Exposition), 1934 - 1937, 1939 (Box 67, Folder 476)
  - Salary Committee Report, 1935 (Box 67, Folder 477)
  - Chief Engineer's Report (related correspondence only) and miscellaneous or general, 1935 - 1938, 1943, n.d. (Box 67, Folder 478)
  - Rules and Policies, 1936, 1937, n.d. (Box 67, Folder 479)
  - Appointment of F.V.K. to Golden Gate Bridge Board and failure of reappointment, 1929 - 1944, n.d. (Box 67, Folder 480)
  - Contracts and Specifications: Vols. 2 - 8, which are Contracts IA-IB, II - X; Specifications for Construction of Superstructure of Main and Side Spans; Land and Water Test Borings at Sites of Main Piers and Anchorages, 1928 - 1929 (Box 68, Folder 481)
  - Blueprints on Bridge and Approaches, 1933 (Box 68, Folder 482)
  - Golden Gate Bridge and Highway District California, and Annual Reports 1935 - 1938 (Box 68, Folder 483)
  - Golden Gate Bridge and Highway District Annual Reports, 1949 - 1956 (Box 68, Folder 484)
  - "The Golden Gate Bridge at San Franciso, Report of Traffic Engineer," Sydney W. Taylor, Jr., 1936, Sept. (Box 68, Folder 485)
  - Clippings (Box 68, Folder 486)
  - Pamphlets (Box 68, Folder 487)
  - Magazine Articles (Box 68, Folder 488)
  - Scrapbook, 1925 - 1934, Jan. 3. (Box 69)
  - Scrapbook, 1934, Jan. - 1936, Dec. 3 (Box 70)
  - Scrapbook, 1936, Dec. 4 - 1937, Dec. 28 (Box 71)
- Series E. San Francisco Earthquake, 1906.
  - San Francisco Earthquake -- clips, 1906, Apr. - May (Box 72)
  - San Francisco Earthquake -- National Guard Report, Observation etc. some clips, photos and misc. material (Box 73)
- Series F. Stanford Material
  - Stanford Associates 1936 (Box 74, Folder 489)
  - Stanford Associates 1937 (Box 74, Folder 490)
  - Stanford Associates 1938 (Box 74, Folder 491)
  - Stanford Associates 1939 (Box 74, Folder 492)
  - Stanford Associates 1940 (Box 74, Folder 493)
  - Stanford Associates 1941 - 1942 (Box 74, Folder 494)
  - Articles re: FVK in Stanford Periodicals (Box 75, Folder 495)
  - Misc. Stanford. Alumni, trustees, student affairs committee, T.G. Crothers correspondence with H. Davis, Pacific Improvement Co. 1908 - 1912 (Box 75, Folder 496)